Hey, Li Wen.
I got scammed.
This sublandlord...
He's a scammer.
The landlord just kicked me out.
Don't panic.
Just take your time and tell me.
I rented a place.
The guy told me if I paid a year's rent,
I'd get a thousand off each month.
So I paid it.
Gu Ting, listen.
Send me the sublandlord's info first.
Okay.
Gu Ting, I found him.
This sublandlord's methods aren't very clever.
He has another property listed for rent,
so he hasn't skipped town yet.
Listen, I'll go stake him out.
I should be able to catch him.
Okay. Thank you.
Old Gu.
Gu Ting got scammed.
Who are you?
You're the one who scammed my friend out of thirty thousand, huh?
Give back the money.
Don't run!
Who's there?
You've got a lot of nerve.
Boss Gu.
You dare scam my sweetie out of her money?
You wanna die?
Boss Gu.
I didn't know she was your daughter.
Well, I'll make sure you know right now!
You wrong my sweetie, you die.
Gu Yan.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Think about Gu Ting.
Put the knife down.
Leave yourself a way out.
Put it away.
He's not worth it.
You hear me?
Talk. Where's the money?
It's already been transferred.
There's only five thousand left.
You...
Five thousand?
You scammed at least three people today.
Let me tell you,
you'd better cough up every last cent.
Now get the hell out of here.
Wait, why did you let him go?
Relax, someone will arrest him.
Don't worry.
Oh, right.
Call Gu Ting right now.
She just got scammed,
so she must be feeling terrible.
Right.
Hurry up.
Sweetie.
I got back the money you were scammed out of.
I'll transfer it to you in a minute.
I don't want it.
Come on.
Give your dad some credit for trying.
What kind of attitude is that?
Give me a break.
Catching the scammer was all Li Wen's doing.
What did you even do?
I'll treat Li Wen to a meal.
If you dare show up, I'm never coming home again!
Goodbye.
I heard all of that.
Oh, man.
Looks like you're not invited to dinner.
I'm out of here.
Bye.
What did I do to deserve this?
Still haven't found a place?
Renting has left me traumatized.
Another youth hostel got exposed for hidden cameras last night.
Then just move back home for now.
I'm not going back there.
How about this, then.
I have a spare room at my place.
Don't get the wrong idea.
If you don't mind,
you can stay at my place for the time being.
As for rent and utilities,
we can just split them at market rate.
That works.
But I'll only stay at your place for a month.
I'll move out as soon as I make some money.
Okay.
Then, after your classes,
I'll take you to check it out.
Yeah.
Sweetie,
I brought you your favorite braised chicken.
You'll be staying in this room.
I've already cleaned it up.
Okay.
Your dad.
Kid,
is my sweetie with you?
Stop bothering people for no reason.
Didn't you see the note?
I moved out.
Sweetie,
you don't understand.
It's a treacherous world out there.
You can't handle it.
I can't believe you don't trust your dad,
and you trust an outsider.
How long have you even known him?
If you don't change your ways,
I'm never going back.
You just can't keep a grown daughter.
I spent 20 years raising her,
only to raise an enemy.
Why don't you reconsider?
Get some rest. See you tomorrow.
I'll eat it if you don't.
So much for my sweet little girl.
I was just thinking about getting back at my dad.
I can't believe I actually moved in.
But...
He doesn't think I'm that kind of...
...easy girl, does he?
But the contract is already signed.
He wouldn't get the wrong idea, right?
I can't believe she's actually staying.
When do you plan
on proposing to me?
Why didn't you give me any warning?
Will you marry me?
From now on,
for the rest of your life,
you're stuck with me.
There's no escaping.
No, no, no!
She's Gu Ting,
not Sun Yao.
You got a death wish?
Lying to both me and Tingting.
Don't you get it?
Gu Ting is dead set on getting rid of you.
I'm just an excuse.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you.
Tingting is my life.
If you dare hurt her,
I'll make you pay.
You've already hurt her,
haven't you?
I'll help you one last time.
After that,
whatever it takes,
you convince Tingting to come back.
Still coding this late?
Weren't you going to write a novel?
I bought you some reference books.
And some mystery collections.
Not sure if they'll help you.
I just made that up.
About writing a detective novel.
I didn't expect her to remember.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
I have a gift for you.
Why did you get me this?
Do you like it?
I love it.
But...
But why did you get me a gift?
You study medicine, after all.
Time is crucial.
Wearing a watch...
...will be more convenient.
I'm sorry. For Yaoyao's sake...
...I have to let you down for now.
By the way, Gu Ting,
there's something...
I think right now,
it's not very convenient for you to stay at my place.
Why?
We've only known each other for a short time.
If you keep staying here,
your dad will be worried sick.
True,
your dad does have a bad temper.
But he's a good person.
How about you go back home for a while?
And have a good talk with him.
Did my dad come looking for you?
No, no, no.
I knew it.
Otherwise, how could you...
...suddenly kick me out for no reason?
No, Gu Ting.
Don't be afraid. I'll go back and confront him right now.
No, no.
Gu Ting!
Didn't I tell you to stop bothering Li Wen?
I didn't!
You still say you didn't?
He's such a good-tempered person.
If you hadn't threatened him,
why would he kick me out?
Good-tempered?
You must be talking about a saint.
Let me tell you,
that Li Wen...
he threatened me!
He's a terrible person!
All right, enough.
You've said that a million times.
I thought you'd show some remorse.
But you're still exactly the same.
I mean, he's such a kind person.
Why do you have to target him?
And even get violent?
Are you going to commit a crime next?
I didn't!
I'm truly so disappointed in you.
Let me tell you this,
I'm going to keep staying at Li Wen's place.
If you dare harass him again,
I'm never coming back to this house.
Li Wen!